(Penny:)You know, it is normal
(Penny:)to want to change your
look after a breakup.
(Amy:)Actually, I was thinking
of making one small change.
(Bernadette:)Your sweater?
Your glasses?
(Bernadette:)Your hair?
Your shoes!
(Amy:)Piercing my ears.
(Raj:)Oh.
Oh.
(Bernadette:)You really never
had that done?
(Amy:)My mom said pierced ears
(Amy:)were for whores,
pirates and genies.
(Penny:)Okay, well, you're
a grown woman now.
(Amy:)I know, but Sheldon
had this clause
(Amy:)in the Relationship Agreement
(Amy:)forbidding cosmetic surgery
(Amy:)unless it's to look
like a Klingon.
(Bernadette:)We'll take you to the
mall to get it done.
(Penny:)Why? I can do it
right here.
(Amy:)Really?
(Amy:)You have a piercing gun?
No.
(Penny:)All you need is a needle
and an ice cube.
(Penny:)I've done it, like,
a dozen times.
(Amy:)Oh, I don't know.
(Penny:)Oh, come on.
I'll be gentle.
(Penny:)Let me take your ear virginity.
(Bernadette:)This party's weird.
(Leonard:)Hey, watch your speed.
(Leonard:)I hear the Mexican police
target tourists.
(Howard:)Oh, not a problem.